A Guide to the Weaver-Brady Papers
University of Virginia Library
Rhodes, J. N. (In non correspondence)
Richard, Henry (In non correspondence)
Risk, Harvey (In non correspondence)
Robertson (Theo.) & Co. (In non correspondence -receipts)
Robertson & Brownlee, Richmond, Va. (1855 June 25, ALS, to W. W., re: general business affairs)
Rogers, William P. (In non correspondence)
Rose, Denison (In non correspondence)
Rose (James) & Co., Lynchburg, Va. (1829 Jan. 5, ALS, to W. W., re: delivery of beaver) (1829 Apr. 10, ALS, to W. W., re: note of Mrs. Spenner) (1829 May 23, ALS, to W. W., re: note for $100)
Rose, William (1830 June 15, ALS, to W. W., re: pig [iron] contract, Weaver as possible Director of Bank of Lynchburg)
Ross & Preston (In non correspondence)
Ruff, John (In non correspondence)
Ruff, Ayres & Co. (1859 Feb. 12, ALS, to W. W., re: 100 lbs. of horse shoe iron)
Salling, A. R. (In non correspondence)
Salling, George J. (1859 Jan. 5, ALS, to W. W., re: making of some clothes for some individual) (1859 Feb. 27, ALS, to W. W., re: loan) (1859 Mar. 8, ALS, to W. W., re: request to give F. Guggenheim $5.00) (1859 Sept. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: 200 lbs of iron) (1859 Nov. 27, ALS, to W. W., re: affairs with his mother)
Salling, Mrs. Lucy W. (1859 Aug. 6, ALS, to Brady, re: Sam's illness) (1859 Aug. 17, ALS, to Brady, re: illness) (1861 Jan. 6, ALS, to W. W., re: hiring Sam) (1862 Jan. 3, ALS, to W. W., re: request for pay of hire of Sam) (In non correspondence -receipt)
Salling, Peter A. (1853 Feb. 15, ALS, to W. W. and Col. Jordan, re: deposition of Jn. Poague)
Sanders, James R. (1859 July 22, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (In non correspondence)
Schoolfield, John W. (1828 Jan. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: spider lids) (1829 Jan. 30, ALS, to W. W., re: arrival of boats) (1829 Jan. 30, ALS, to W. W., re: demand of bar steel) (1829 Feb. 13, ALS, to W. W., re: destitution of Ben Armstrong) (1829 Feb. 20, ALS, to W. W, re: Weaver's account to Schoolfield) (1829 Mar. 19, ALS, to W. W., re: note and loan) (1829 Mar. 20, ALS, to W. W., re: order of iron bars end ploughs) (1829 Apr. 10, ALS, to W. W., re: favor of Ben Armstrong) (1829 June 23, ALS, to W. W., re: refusal to receive an order of iron) (1829 June 25, ALS, to W. W., re: note of Capt. Dudley) (1829 Dec. 3, ALS, to W. W., re: order of wool hats and stove pipe) (1829 Dec. 14, ALS, to W. W., re: receipt of bar iron from John Cuminger) (1831 Apr. 19, ALS, to A. Davis, re: light weight iron order) (1831 Aug. 5, ALS, to W. W., re: forwarding acct.) (1831 Aug. 26, ALS, to W. W., re: bill of article sent by Moses) (In non correspondence)
Shepherd, A. L. [attorney], Richmond, Va. (1861 Mar. 11, ALS, to W. W., re: Weaver's acct.)
Sherrerd, Samuel (1849 Feb. 1, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: statement of metal delivered) (In non correspondence)
Shields, Cana (In non correspondence -receipts)
Shields and Sommerville, Richmond, Va. (1859 Feb. 8, ALS, to W. W., re: sale of 100 tons of Etna metal) (1859 Aug. 3, ALS, to W. W., re: price negotiations for metal) (1859 Aug. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: need of money) (1859 Sept. 3, ALS, to W. W., re: bank problems) (1859 Sept. 16, ALS, to W. W., re: Shook's estate) (1859 Oct. 13, ALS, to W. W., re: note for ca. $500) (1861 Feb.11, ALS to W. W., re: Mr. Anderson, metal purchase) (1861 Apr. 6, ALS, to W. W., re: request for metal)
Shirkey, John (1830 Sept. 26, ALS, to W. W., re: bacon delivery)
Sledon, [J. M.] (In non correspondence)
Slow, John A. (In non correspondence)
Smith (A. and; D.) (In non correspondence)
Smith, George W. (In non correspondence -receipts)
Smith, Samuel R. (1831 Aug. 25, ALS, to W. W., re: half dozen gilt chairs)
Snyder, Asa (1861 Jan. 18, ALS, to W. W., re: Etna pig iron) (1861 July 8, ALS, to W. W., re: order of iron for stoves) (1861 Sept. 11, ALS, to W. W., re: request for sample of iron) (1861 Sept 19, ALS, to W. W., re: letter for notice that former letter has been sent) (1861 Nov. 19, ALS, to W. W., re: irate letter requesting what happened to iron purchased) (1862 Jan. 30, ALS, to W. W., re: inquiry into why iron was not recieved) (1862 Feb. 7, ALS, to W. W., re:inquiry into why iron has not been received) (1862 Feb. 17, ALS, to W. W., re: Snyder's account with Weaver)
Sommerville (R. B.) and Co., Richmond, Va. (1861 Apr. 9, ALS, to W. W., re: general business affairs) (1861 May 1, ALS, to W. W., re: sale of iron) (1861 May 6, ALS, to W. W., re: W. W. has no metal for sale) (1861 July 17, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1861 Sept. 18, Als, to W. W., re: possibility of iron sales in the future) (1861 Nov. 7, ALS, to W. W., re: general business news) (1861 Nov. 19, ALS, to W. W., re: inquiry into missing metal) (1862 Jan. 21, ALS, to W. W., re: request for reply to previous letter) (1862 Jan. 30, ALS, to W. W., re: confirmation of metal sale) (1862 Jan 31, ALS, to W. W., re: metal order) (1862 Mar. 4, ALS, to W. W., re: arrival of W. H. Smoot) (1862 Mar. 6, ALS, to W. W., re: general business affairs) (1862 Mar. 12, ALS, to W. W., re: acct. of iron sales) (1862 July 28, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order)
Sowers, John C. (1829 Nov. 5, ALS, to W. W., re: price of linen)
Staples, James (1828 Mar. 11, ALS, [W. W.] to Staples, re: promise to pay $84.72)
Stapels, William (1830 Jan. 4, ALS, to W. W., re: return of a hired worker, Isaac)
Steele, Joseph G. [Notary Public] (In non correspondence --legal)
Sterrett, Robert (1832 Sept. 29, ALS, to W. W., re: Weaver's note to Sterrett)
Stevens, W. (In non correspondence)
Stokely, D. Q. (In non correspondence)
Stokely, [T.] (In non correspondence)
[Sturrett], John (1847 Oct. 1, ALS, to W. W., re: borrow money from Weaver to go west)
Switzer, Newton (1861 July 9, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1862 Oct. 14, ALS to W. W., re: iron order) (1862 Dec. 30, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order)
Tabor, John (1846 Sept. 21, ALS, W. W. to Tabor, re: railroad iron)
Talbot, H. E. (1891 Mar. 27, ALS, to Wm. A. Anderson, re: meeting Anderson, purchase of land)
Taylor, J. McDowell (1859 Jan.7, ALS, to W. W. (?), re: axles) (1859 Jan. 25, ALS, to W. W., re: pattern for an axle) (1859 Dec., ALS, to W. W., re: wagon tires)
Taylor, James S. (In non correspondence)
Taylor, William (1830 June 29, ALS, to W. W., re: Dannenhower draft on W. W.)
Taylor and Humphries (1859 July 12, ALS, to W. W., re: tumbling shaft)
Tinsley, Robert (In non correspondence)
Tomey, William W. (1859 Sept. 20, ALs, to W. W., re: farm tenants)
Tompkins (W. D.) and Bro., Richmond, Va. (1859 May 17, ALS, to W. W., re: bill for articles ordered) (1859 June 1, ALS, to W. W., re: clothes order) (1859 June 7, ALS, to W. W., re: general business) (1859 Sept. 19, ALS, to W. W., re: flour order) (1859 Oct. 12, ALS, to W. W., re: Weaver's acct. with Tompkins) (1859 Oct. 20, ALS, to W. W., re: Weaver's bill with Tompkins) (1859 Oct. 29, ALS, to W. W., re: plaster) (1861 Mar. 23, ALS, to W. W., re: Weaver's acct.) (1861 July 2, ALS, to W. W., re: clothes) (1861 July 10, ALS, to W. W., re: Weaver's bill) (1862 Jan. 16, ALS, to W. W., re: articles Weaver ordered) (1862 Jan. 28, ALS, to W. W., re: salt, corn) (1862 Feb. 13, ALS, to W. W., re: list and delivery of articles) (1862 Feb. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1862 Mar. 3, ALS, to W. W., re: arrival of William A. Smoot) (1862 Mar. 25, ALS, to W. W., re: Weaver's acct.) (1862 Apr. 2, ALS, to W. W., re: business affairs) (1862 Apr. 16, ALS, to W. W., re: bill of W. W.) (1862 Sept. 10, ALS, to W. W., re: notice of receipt of order) (1862 Nov. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: tar) (1862 Dec.6, ALS, to W. W., re: supplies ordered) (In non correspondence)
Treavey and Jackson (In non correspondence)
Tums, William (In non correspondence)
Turpin, Vincent (1860 Nov. 6, ALS, to Greenlee Davidson, re: Joseph Reed's note to W. W.)
Updike, J. G. (1859 Apr. 8, ALS, to W. W., re: request for seed oats)
Van Lingen, George A. (1891, ALS, C. C. Jones to Randolph Barton and Van Lingen, re: bill)
Varner, Charles (In non correspondence)
Virginia. Board of Public Works (1854 May 24, ALS, W. W. to Va. Board of Public Works, re: bridge at Buffalo in Rockbridge Co.)
Virginia. County Court (Rockbridge Co.) (In non correspondence)
Waggoner, Hill and Archer, Richmond, Va. (1861 Jan. 21, ALS, to W. W., re: slowness of business)
[Watts], Joseph (1831 Mar. 17, ALS, to A. W. Davis, re: bacon purchase)
Weaver, William, 1780-1863 (1828 Mar. 11, ALS, [W. W.] to Jas. Staples, re: promise to pay $84. 72) (1840 Feb. 20, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: crops from 1825-1830; Mr. Barker's) (1841 Apr. 17, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: suit of Baldwin) (1845 Nov. 3, ALS, to P. K. Gorgas, re: Jas. Barclay's land) (1846 July 21, ALS, to P. K. Gorgas, re: payment of some debts) (1846 Sept. 21, ALS, to John Tabor, re: railroad iron) (1846 Sept. 21, ALS, to P. K. Gorgas, re: railroad iron) (1848 July 23, ALS, to J. D. Davisdon, re: unidentifiable legal business) (1849 Nov. 12, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: Sherrerd's 1849 statement) (1849 Nov. 25, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: orders for Davidson) (1849 Dec. 7, ALS, to Jn. Letcher, re: sawmill and sawing) (1850 Dec. 15, ALS, to ? (only 2nd page of letter), re: learning institutions of Va.) (1851 Dec. 15, ALS, to Jn. Jordan, re: disputed land boundary) (1852 Jan. 10, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: bond; Baldwin case) (1852 Sept. 4, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: agricultural products) (1854 [Jan. 4], ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: business with Mr. Barclay) (1854 May 1, AlS, to J. D. Davidson, re: takeover of some unidentified property) (1854 May 21, ALS, to J. D. Davisdon, re: payment of Barclay for land) (1854 May 24, ALS, to Board of Public Works of Va., re: bridge at Buffalo in Rockbridge Co.) (1855 Apr. 16, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: payment of $300) (1855 May 5, ALS to ?, re: J. Moore) (1855 July 12, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: a note for $284.75) (1855 Sept, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: Camden's residence) (1855 Oct. 5, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: meeting with Wm. Davidson) (1855 Oct. 22, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: W. W. going to Richmond) (1856 Mar. 5, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: W. W.'s birthday party) (1856 Apr. 2, ALS, to ?, re: social engagement) (1856 Apr. 8, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: invitation) (1856 May 18, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: Murray's affairs) (1856 July 12, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: Grigsby's letters) (1856 Nov. 12, ALS, to ?, re: Mr. Letcher to come see Weaver) (1856 Nov. 21, ALS, to ?, re: invitation) (1858 Mar. 4, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: general business affairs) (1858 Aug. 4, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: general business affairs) (1859 Jan. 8, ALS, to ?, re: furnace and business) (1859 Dec. 16, ALS, to ?, re: general business affairs) (1863, appraisal of Weaver's goods and chattels) (n.d., ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: deeds, business) (n.d., ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: copy of notice served to T. Jordan -in 1849 folder)
Webb (Lewis) and Co., Richmond, Va. (1827 Mar. 20, ALS, to W. W., re: ordr of Wm. Palmer) (1828 Mar. 1, ALS, to W. W., re: contract with Charles) (1828 June 7, ALS, to W. W., re: boots) (1828 June 9, ALS, to W. W., re: bill for boots) (1828 Aug. 9, ALS, to W. W., re: iron sales) (1828 Sept. 4, ALS, to W. W., re: iron shipment) (1828 Nov. 12, ALS, to W. W., re: iron sales) (1828 Nov. 22, ALS to W. W., re: accounts from Liverpool) (1828 Nov 25, ALS, to W. W., re: boots; shipments from Europe) (1828 Dec. 6, ALS, to W. W., re: prices of corn and whiskey) (1828 Dec. 18. ALS, to W. W., re: authorization for draft for $1750) (1828 Dec. 22, ALS, to W. W., re: boots refund) (1829 Jan. 20, ALS, to W. W., re: accounts from England) (1829 Feb. 5, ALS, to W. W., re: payment for pigs) (1829 Feb. 7, ALS, to W. W., re: credit) (1829 Feb 23, ALS, to W. W., re: settlement with Clarke) (1829 Mar. 4, ALS, to W. W., re: rolling iron) (1829 Mar. 14, ALS, to W. W., re: boots) (1829 Mar. 28, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1829 May 20, ALS, to W. W., re: price of iron) (1829 June 16, ALS, to W. W., re: iron shipments) (1829 Aug. 18, ALS, to W. W., re: bar iron order) (1829 Sept. 28, ALS, to W. W., re: overdrawn account) (1829 Oct. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: shipment from England) (In non correspondence)
Webb, W. B. (1859 Jan. 9, ALS ,to W. W., re: job as overseer) (1859 Jan. 25, ALS, to W. W., re: arrival of John McKnight) (1859 Feb. 13, ALS, to W. W., re: reason Webb has not come to the forge)
Whitcomb, H. D. (1856 June 20, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: Weaver's land at Panther Gap)
Whitmore, John (1829 Oct. 13, ALS, J. Danenhower to Whitmore, re: grinding of 20 bushels of corn and 20 bushels of rye)
Wiglesworth, John (1829 Jan. 5, ALS, to W. W., re: hiring of slaves) (1830 Jan. 20, ALS, to W. W., re: a forwarded letter)
Williams, Samuel S. (1828 Dec. 17, ALS, to W. W., re: beef shipment) (1829 Nov. 4, ALS, to W. W., re: purchase of articles in Lynchburg)
Williams, Taylor B. (In non correspondence)
Willmeth, William (In non correspondence --1859)
Willoughby, Robert F. (1861 Jan. 8, ALS, to Brady, re: hands) (1861 Jan. 28, ALS, to Brady, re: price of slave)
Wilson, D. J. (1839 May 25, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: Maybury-Weaver suit)
Wirts, John (1824 Jan. 31, ALS, to W. W., re: Gullens case) (1824 Feb. 4, ALS, to W. W., re: cases against Garrigues and Conrad) (1824 Oct. 19, ALS, to W. W., re: Garrigues case) (1829 Feb. 20, ALS, to W. W., re: Conrad's rent) (1829 Mar. 30, ALS, to W. W., re: Garrigues case) (1829 July 9, ALS, to W. W., re: absence of Wirts) (1830 Mar. 9, ALS, to W. W., re: mortgage suit)
Young, Benjamin (1829 Feb. 4, ALS, to W. W., re: raising of hogs) (1829 Aug. 11, ALS, to W. W., re: hogs)
Container List
- Letters
  - Letters, 1824 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1827 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1828, Jan.-July (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1828, Aug.-Dec. (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1829, Jan.-Feb. (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1829, Mar.-Apr. (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1829, May-Dec. (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1830 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1831, Jan.-May (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1831, June-Dec. (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1832 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1833 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1835 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1837-1839 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1840-1844 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1845-1846 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1847-1849 (Box Box 1)
  - Page of a letter, 1850 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1851-1852 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1853-1854 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1855 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1856-1857 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1858 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1859, Jan.-Mar (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1859, Apr.-July (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1859, Aug (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, etc., 1859, Sept.-Oct. (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1859, Nov.-Dec. (Box Box 1)
  - Letter, 1860 (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1861, Jan.-Apr. (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1861, May-Dec. (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1862, Jan.-Mar. (Box Box 1)
  - Letters, 1862, Apr.-Dec. (Box Box 2)
  - W. B. Kayser to D. C. E. Brady, 1877 Dec.; ALS (Box Box 2)
  - C. K. Bullock to C. H. Brady, 1879 April; ALS (Box Box 2)
  - Letters of B. M. Allen, 1881 (Box Box 2)
  - Letters, 1891 (Box Box 2)
  - W. W. to Jas. D. Davidson, n.d.; ALS (Box Box 2)
- Financial and Legal Papers
  - Financial Papers, 1814 (Box Box 2)
  - Financial papers and Legal Documents, 1830-1840 (Box Box 2)
  - Notes, receipts, and financial papers, 1831 (Box Box 2)
  - Legal Documents and Business Papers, 1840-1845 (Box Box 2)
  - Documents, Business Papers, 1846-1850 (Box Box 2)
  - Cash Book and Wood Book, 1849-1852 (Box Box 2)
  - Documents, Personal, financial Business Papers, 1850-1855 (Box Box 2)
  - Documents, Business Accounts, 1856-1858 (Box Box 2)
  - Accounts, business papers, 1859, Jan.-Mar. (Box Box 2)
  - Financial Papers, 1859, Apr.-July (Box Box 2)
  - Receipts, Financial papers, 1859, Aug.-Dec. (Box Box 2)
  - Circular to Friends and Patrons of Rural Empire Club, 1861 (Box Box 2)
  - Receipts and Financial papers, 1861-1862 (Box Box 2)
  - Appraisement of goods and chattels of William Weaver, deceased, 1863 (Box Box 2)
  - Financial Papers, 1863-1864 (Box Box 2)
  - Registration Oaths, etc., 1867 (Box Box 2)
  - Registration Certificates, Financial Papers, etc., 1870 (Box Box 2)
  - Financial Papers, etc., 1871 (Box Box 3)
  - No Trespassing Notices, 1872, June 11 (Box Box 3)
  - Financial Papers, etc., 1872 (Box Box 3)
  - Warrants Paid (Bundled together and labelled), 1872-1873 (Box Box 3)
  - Financial Papers, etc., 1873 (Box Box 3)
  - Financial Papers, etc., 1874 (Box Box 3)
  - Financial Papers, etc., 1875 (Box Box 3)
  - Receipts, etc., 1876 (Box Box 3)
  - Receipts, etc., 1877 (Box Box 3)
  - Fragments, Miscellany, n.d. (Box Box 3)
  - Fragments of a Journal, n.d. (Box Box 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, n.d. (Box Box 3)
- Ledgers
  - I. Boxed Ledgers, etc.
    - Bath Furnace Negro Book, 1827-1829 (Box Box 1)
    - Buffalo Forge Time Book, 1843-1853 (Box Box 1)
    - Buffalo Forge Day Book (includes Union Forge), 1825-1826 (Box Box 1)
    - Buffalo Forge Day Book, 1841-1844 (Box Box 1)
    - Buffalo Forge Day Book, 1867-1868 (Box Box 2)
    - Buffalo Forge Day Book, 1869 -1871 (Box Box 2)
    - Buffalo Forge Day Book, 1871-1873 (Box Box 2)
    - Springs Mills Journal, 1872-1874 (Box Box 2)
    - Springs Mills Journal, 1875 (Box Box 2)
    - Springs Mills Journal, 1876-1877 (Box Box 2)
    - Springs Mills Journal, 1873-1877 (Box Box 2)
    - Bath Iron Works Day Book, 1813-1823 (Box Box 3)
    - Bath Iron Works Negro Book, 1839-1842 (Box Box 3)
    - Bath Iron Works Negro Book, 1846 (Box Box 3)
    - Bath Iron Works Ledger, 1828-1834 (Box Box 3)
    - Bath Iron Works Ledger, 1828-1830 (Box Box 3)
    - Etna Furnace Day Book, 1858-1859 (Box Box 4)
    - Etna Furnace Day Book, 1859-1862 (Box Box 4)
    - Etna Furnace Time Book, 1854-1858 (Box Box 4)
    - Etna Furnace Time Book, 1855-1861 (Box Box 4)
    - Etna Furnace Time Book, 1867 (Box Box 4)
    - Etna Furnace Journal, 1858-59 (Box Box 5)
    - Etna Furnace Ledger, 1856-57 (Box Box 5)
    - Buffalo Forge Time Book, 1872-74 (Box Box 5)
    - Buffalo Forge Time Book and Wood Records, 1830-1843 (Box Box 5)
    - Bath Furnace Provision Book, 1839 (Box Box 6)
    - Provision Books: Lower Mill, Buffalo Forge, 1865 and 1870-1872 (Box Box 6)
    - Buffalo Forge Dairy Book, 1866-1867 (Box Box 6)
    - Daniel C. E. Brady Home and Farm Journal, 1858 (Box Box 6)
    - Letterbook 1859-60 (Box Box 6)
    - Bank Book of William Weaver, 1860-1863 (Box Box 6)
    - Buffalo Forge Negro Book, 1865 (Box Box 6)
    - Unidentified Day Book, 1838-1842 (Box Box 6)
    - Unidentified Day Book, 1839-1841 (Box Box 7)
    - Unidentified Day Book, 1841-1844 (Box Box 7)
    - Unidentified Ledger, 1825-26 (Box Box 7)
    - Unidentified Ledger, 1825-1829 (Box Box 7)
    - Bath Iron Works Ledger (contains negro accounts), 1837-1841 (Box Box 8)
    - Unidentified Ledger, 1838-1840 (Box Box 8)
    - Unidentified Ledger, 1841-1844 (Box Box 8)
    - Unidentified Ledger, 1878 (Box Box 9)
    - Unidentified Ledger, 1867 (Box Box 9)
    - Unidentified Ledger, 1871-72 (Box Box 9)
    - Unidentified Ledger, 1845-52 (Box Box 9)
  - II. Unboxed Ledgers, etc
    - Buffalo Forge Negro Book, 1830-1840; 1.
    - Buffalo Forge Negro Book, 1839-1841; 2.
    - Buffalo Forge Negro Book, 1844-1848; 3.
    - Buffalo Forge Negro Book, 1850-1857; 4.
    - Buffalo Forge Journal, 1834-1841; 5.
    - Buffalo Forge Day Book, 1857-186?; 6.
    - Buffalo Forge Journal, 1828-1833; 7.
    - Buffalo Forge Journal, 1845-1850; 8.
    - Buffalo Forge Journal, 1850-1859; 9.
    - Buffalo Forge Journal, 1859-1866; 10.
    - Buffalo Forge Iron Book, 1832-1862; 11.
    - Buffalo Forge Day Book, Liberty Furnace, 1854-1858; 12.
    - Springs Mills Journal, 1869-1870; 13.
    - Spring Mills Journal, 1877 -?; 14.
    - Bath Iron Works Day Book, 1833-1834; 15.
    - Bath Iron Works Day Book, 1837-1844; 16.
    - Bath Iron Works Day Book, 1849-1859, D.C.E. Brady Home Journal, 1858-1860, 1849-1860; 17.
    - Bath Iron Works Journal, 1828-1829; 18.
    - Bath Iron Works Day Book and Letter Book, 1844-1847; 19.
    - Bath Iron Works Cash Book, 1849-1862; 20.
    - Etna Furnace Negro Book, 1854-56; 21.
    - Etna Furnace Negro Book, 1857-1859; 22.
    - Etna Furnace White Hands Book, 1861; 23.
    - Etna Furnace Ledger, 1854-1866; 24.
    - Etna Furnace Ledger, 1858-1861; 25.
    - Unidentified Ledger, 1828-1840; 26.
    - Unidentified Ledger, 1828-1837; 27.
    - Unidentified Day Book, 1864-1866; 28.
    - Unidentified Day Book, 1842-1843; 29.
    - Unidentified Day Book, 1877-1878; 30.
    - Unidentified Day Book, 1846; 31.
    - Unidentified Day Book, 1862-1864; 32.
    - Unidentified Journal, 1841-1844; 33.
    - Unidentified Journal, 1867-1870; 34.
    - Unidentified Journal, 1867-1868; 35.
    - Unidentified Provision Book, 1843-1846; 36.